<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Send SMS on time</string>

    <string name="messageTextView">There is no message to send</string>

    <string name="messageButton">TAP TO PROVIDE MESSAGE</string>

    <string name="dateTextView">The date is not set</string>

    <string name="dateButton">TAP TO SET DATE</string>

    <string name="contactTextView">Contacts were not selected</string>

    <string name="contactButton">TAP TO SELECT CONTACT</string>

    <string name="sendMessageCheckBox">Send a message</string>

    <string name="exitButton">EXIT</string>

    <string name="clearButton">CLEAR ALL DATA</string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy"> PRIVACY POLICY</string>
    <string name="title_activity_privacy_policy">PRIVACY POLICY</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_text">

        "The privacy policy of the mobile application Send SMS on time.\n\n"

        "1.\n\n"

        "This document describes the privacy policy of the mobile application Send SMS on time. "
        "The developer of the application treats the protection of privacy on the Internet Users "
        "using the mobile application Send SMS on time via Google Play Store as a priority and "
        "makes every effort to protect this privacy.\n\n"

        "2.\n\n"

        "The application Send SMS on time is installed on mobile devices, in particular on mobile "
        "phones and tablets after downloading it from Google Play Store.\n\n"

        "3.\n\n"

        "Using the application requires a mobile device with Android - version min. 6.0 with an "
        "active SIM card installed.\n\n"

        "4.\n\n"

        "Using the application doesn’t require providing any user personal data. The application "
        "doesn’t store any personal data that could enable a third party to identify a specific "
        "user of the application.\n\n"

        "5.\n\n"

        "The application Send SMS on time needs access the following permissions on a mobile "
        "device:\n"
            "•	sending an SMS\n"
            "•	reading an SMS\n"
            "•	contact lists\n"
        "Application permissions can be revoked by changing the system settings on the device or "
        "uninstalling the application.\n\n"

        "6.\n\n"

        "If you don’t agree to this privacy policy, please don’t install the application or "
        "uninstall it. Permanently deleting the application from the mobile device is tantamount "
        "to terminating use of the application.\n\n"

        "7.\n\n"

        "This privacy policy is only complementary to the Google Play Store privacy policy. The "
        "developer of the application isn’t responsible for the Google Play Store privacy policy "
        "and compliance with the provisions of the Act on the protection of personal data and the "
        "Act on the provision of electronic services as part of the Google Play Store.\n\n"

    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

</resources>
